drama3s.tv 2018-02-03

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to protecting your privacy while online at our website. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website

**Log files**

Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring and exit pages, platform type, date stamped time, and number of clicks to analyze trends and gather personal information for general use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and read the terms of the privacy of each and every website collecting personally identifiable information. This statement applies only to confidential information collected by this website.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
